If you're a spandex fan you cannot miss this video because I'm going to show you
the new LeoHex spandex rompers. I have different colors and I think it's a
funny look with the short legs like a sports wear romper. Now I'm getting
confused so I will change. I decided to start with blue and as you can see LeoHex
redefined their cut so I have dozens of LeoHex catsuits by now also with long
arms, long legs. They have relatively simple cut but here we have a lot of seams which flow nicely
along the whole body and give sort of like a athletic vibe I'd say. What's also new is this
mesh part here. So second fabric the main part is spandex and it's really soft spandex. It's a really
fine spandex and it's also really stretchy so I can like stretch this and
by the way I'm wearing a size large it is Asian sizing so please be aware of
that and check out the size chart I will switch into the white one now same cut
same material different color it's also the same spandex as the usual leohex
products it says on a front page on amazon that it is not see-through i mean you can clearly see
that it is see-through the white one at least now and i'm also wearing tights so you can see that
too but also my underwear by the way i will link the amazon products in the description text so
you can check that out to order your leo hex right otherwise i think the shine on this one is really
nice like better than on a blue one i'm really curious about the gray one because it is more
my color than white okay gray one and let me check in the mirror because i haven't tried them on yet
yeah definitely my favorite color also the shine is really really nice i mean the term the white
one is I think a romper and they do remind me a lot about the heavy weightlifter suits with the
tiny legs here you know also one way men anyway you can use them for sports of course gymnastics
yoga whatever or with just a few like spandex good thing is that it's really stretchy and really long
so I don't have any problems moving around.
That's really good, especially with my body length of 173cm.
And now I'm going to switch into the last one.
Trying to figure out if I like the colour or not.
It's more like a salmon pink.
It looked less bright on the hanger to be honest and brighter now that I'm wearing it.
But it's also not really bright pink so it's in between.
Not sure about it.
I think if I'm going to wear pink then I would wear rather a in your face neon pink than this kind of salmon.
It's interesting. It does work with the hair of course.
Anyway, you can tell me in the comments which color you like most.
I am definitely going with grey and this one followed by blue.
Alright, as I said, check out the description text for the link and watch my other LeoHacks videos if you're interested in that kind of fashion.
I do have a lot of other stuff on my channel as well like silicon, latex, PVC, PU, on tour wear, visit trade fairs wear, I visit designers festivals.
festival so there's a lot to see have a scroll around leave a thumbs up and subscribe to my
channel if you like it I would love that I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye